You know, I see y'all saying, Amanda, your skin looks so amazing.
Like, what is it?
Well, it's sleep.
It's drinking water.
It's being in nature.
But it's also the fact that I haven't worried about a man calling me back in two years.
I haven't argued about, like, my human existence and how I want to be treated.
With someone who is physically entering my body in two years.
I haven't had to defend my feelings to someone who is physically entering my body in two years.
And that is how you see such a beautiful visage.
I'm back.
Because I don't have toxins entering my system.
Literally entering.
And ain't nobody entering again until they prove they are toxin-free.
But I'm fun.
Talkie, talkie, toxin-free.
Sister Seals.
This is your ancestor.
Harriet Tubman.
Head to AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance and release of my new book,
What Would the Ancestors Say, on November 8th.
Also, check out When I'll Be in Your City with my book tour.
See you then.
Pop, pop.
Let's go.